

EDUCATION

SOFTWARE ENGINEER

Industrial University of HCMC 2013 - 2017

SKILLS

HTML

CSS / Less / Sass

JavaScript

Angular

React

TypeScript

LANGUAGES

VIETNAMESE ENGLISH

Phone

+84 981 540 288

Email

maiquocqui@gmail.com

website

maiquocqui.github.io

Address

50/8/16 Quang Trung, Ward 10, Go Vap District, HCMC

QUI QUOC MAI

SOFTWARE ENGINEER

ABOUT ME

I'm a Software Engineer specializing in front-end development. I have 5+ years of experience in front-end development. Good experienced in modern JS frameworks/libraries Angular, React. Experienced in building and maintaining Responsive Web and Cross-Browser compatibility.

Background in trainer, mentor, team leader.

EXPERIENCE

Apr 2019 - Present

ZALO

Software Engineer

- Develop ads creating and booking tools by using Angular and React.
- Maintain and optimize source code.

Sep 2018 - Apr 2019 Al PACIFIC

Software Engineer

- Develop HRM and HIS web app by using ReactJS.
- Develop native app cross-platforms by using React Native.

Aug 2016 - Jul 2018

CANH CAM

Software Engineer

- Front-end team leader and internship trainer.
- Develop front-end code for 100+ website projects using html/css/jquery and bootstrap framework.
- Develop tools to make the front-end development process more efficient using GulpJS

Sep 2015 - Aug 2016 DERASOFT

Associate Software Engineer

- Create website template using photoshop.
- Develop basic front-end code using html/css/jquery support responsive.